John Rubio

Portfolio: <u>livelifedev.github.io</u> GitHub: <u>github.com/livelifedev</u>

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/john-m-rubio

Northern Beaches, Sydney – 0424 505 157 – johnrubio93@gmail.com

PROFILE SUMMARY

Animation graduate and current tech student working towards a full stack developer career. Strong visual, technical and problem-solving background having studied visual effects and 3D animation. Proficient communication skills with work experience in customer-oriented roles.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- MERN Stack

- Ruby
- Ruby on Rails
- 2D and 3D design
- Git

EDUCATION

Diploma of IT in Web Development

Coder Academy (February 2019 – Present)

Bachelor of Interactive Media in VFX & Animation

SAE Creative Media Institute (February 2012 – February 2015)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Shop Assistant/Weekend Supervisor

Neutral Bay Vinnies (November 2015 – April 2018)

Responsibilities:

- Responsible for opening and closing store
- Managed till and cash flow
- Supervised volunteers and newer staff members
- Managed stock in store front and back

Backpacker Hostel Staff

Various backpacker hostels (April 2016 – July 2017)

Responsibilities:

- Worked in various hostels while travelling
- Welcomed and checked-in guests
- Provided help and information to guests
- Organised hostel activities

Promotion & Sales Rep

Australian Sales and Promotions (February 2015 – October 2015)

Responsibilities:

- Actively engaged with potential customers to promote and sell product
- Listened to customer problems and provided them solution through product
- Provided a great customer experience to leave customer feeling satisfied

PROJECTS

Ruby on Rails App, Lib-U (2019)

An online library service built on Ruby on Rails working in a team of three

https://lib-u.herokuapp.com/

Ruby Terminal App, Plantaro (2019)

A terminal game created using Ruby working in a team of two

https://github.com/livelifedev/plantaro

JavaScript Music Player, dev Tunes (2019)

A web music player created using HTML, CSS, JavaScript

https://github.com/livelifedev/web-player